rileyrose.com 2017-12-16

# Riley Rose

Effective as of February 14, 2017

This Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) tells you how we collect, use and share information we collect on our website www.rileyrose.com (the “Site”) and all other internet properties operated by Innovative Brand Partners, LLC. (“Riley Rose”, “us”, or “we”) that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Sites“).

We understand the importance that our customers place on privacy and have designed this Privacy Policy to describe our information-gathering and dissemination practices. You agree to this Privacy Policy when you: 1) access or use any Site; and/or 2) agree to receive e-mail from us. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. 

Please note that we reserve the right to review and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by means of a general notice on the Sites prior to the change taking effect. If you use a Site after the updated Privacy Policy becomes effective, you will be deemed to have agreed to the amended Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy addresses the following:

  1. Information that we collect about you.
  2. Cookies and other tracking technology that we use.
  3. What we do with the information that we collect.
  4. With whom we share the information we collect.
  5. Our opt-out policy.
  6. Our policy on correcting and updating Personal Information and deactivation of your account.
  7. Miscellaneous.

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

Information Provided by You Upon Registration. When you register for an account on a Site, we may collect the following information that allows us to identify you (“Personal Information“):

  1. Name
  2. Email address
  3. ZIP/Postal Code
  4. Home Phone
  5. Mobile Phone

Information Provided When You Contact Us. We may collect Personal Information that you voluntarily provide to us when you contact us with a question or comment about our products and services. We generally collect one or more of the following types of Personal Information when you contact us with a question or comment or request information from us about our products and services:

  1. Name
  2. Email address
  3. Company Name
  4. Phone Number
  5. Information about your position

Passively Collected Information. When you access our Sites, we automatically collect your computer or device’s internet protocol (IP) address and other technical information about your computer or device and website usage, such as your browser type and version, time zone setting, and operating system and platform. We may also collect information about you through social media sites you use to access our Site depending the permissions you have given for access to your information. We also use cookies on our Sites; for more information, please see the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section below.

Information Collected From Our Partners. We may partner with our third party resellers to receive information about you, such as name and contact information. This helps us to fulfill your service requests and/or to provide you with services that may be of interest to you. 

COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES THAT WE USE

We and our service providers use cookies, beacons, embedded scripts and local shared objects in connection with the Sites.

  * Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or device when you visit our websites. Cookies allow a website to recognize a particular device or browser. The use of cookies is a standard practice among websites to collect information about visitors’ activities while using the website.
  * Beacons are small graphical images (also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) that may be included on our Sites and typically work in conjunction with cookies to identify our users and user behavior.
  * An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.
  * Local Shared Objects. Local shared objects (or Flash cookies) are pieces of data that websites which use Adobe Flash may store on a user’s computer or device. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Sites or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use local shared objects. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing local shared objects. In addition, you may manage Flash cookies by clicking here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

The above technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the Sites, services and products, tracking users’ movements around the Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember users’ settings, market products and services to users, and for authentication purposes. To manage the cookies that are placed on your computer, you may configure your internet browser to refuse, accept or delete cookies from our Sites at any time. The help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if cookies are disabled or removed, not all features of our Sites will operate as intended.

Third-Party Advertising Services: We partner with third parties that may use technologies such as cookies (and local stored objects as described above) to gather information about your activities on the Sites and elsewhere on the Internet in order to provide you with relevant advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. This type of advertising is sometimes called interest-based advertising. If you wish to not have this information collected and used for interest-based advertising, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/?pid=truste01&aid=preference_manager01&type=public) for partners that participate in the TRUSTe opt-out tool (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). If you wish to opt-out from this type of advertising for companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), you can do so [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/). Please note that this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. Riley Rose adheres to the DAA’s Self-Regulatory Principles.

Third-Party Analytics. We may also use service providers, such as Google Analytics, that may use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your online activities across this and other sites over time for non-advertising purposes such as those described above. To learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data and the choices Google may offer to control these activities, you may visit <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/>

WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

As examples of how we may use Personal Information that we collect, we use Personal Information in the following ways:

  * Information Provided By You Upon Registration and Making a Purchase. We may use this Personal Information to administer your access to a Site, verify your identity, and provide our products or services to you.
  * Information Provided When You Contact Us. We may use this Personal Information to understand and respond to your question or comment.
  * General Uses. We may also use your Personal Information to improve and personalize your experience with us, and, with your consent where necessary, send you information about us and keep you informed of our other products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * Passively Collected Information. We use passively collected information to monitor and maintain the performance of our Sites, analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our services, validate users and ensure their technological compatibility with users, and optimize our marketing efforts.
  * Aggregate data. We may use your Personal Information to create aggregate data which does not include any Personal Information and which cannot be used to identify you. For example, aggregate data may include data that describes the general demographics, usage or other characteristics of a Site’s users. We reserve the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about a Site’s users for lawful purposes.

EU Residents - International Transfers of Personal Information. The Personal Information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA“) in reliance on a variety of compliance mechanisms, including data processing agreements based on the EU Standard Contractual Clauses. It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your Personal Information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

WITH WHOM WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise with your permission. We reserve the right to transfer and/or sell other data, including aggregate or de-identified data derived from Personal Information, for lawful purposes in our discretion.

  * We may share Personal Information with affiliated businesses. 
  * Service Providers. We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies (“Service Providers“) to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, and hosting services. When we employ a Service Provider to perform a function of this nature, we provide it with the information that it needs to perform its specific function, which may include Personal Information and other information that you provide to us via a Site. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * Third Parties for Marketing and Other Purposes. We may share with selected third party partners, including for their direct marketing purposes (please see below for your choices related to this sharing).
  * Legal Requirements. We may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a subpoena or similar legal obligation, (b) protect and defend our rights or property, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of any Site or the public, (d) protect against legal liability, or (e) or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
  * Business Transfers. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, total or partial sale of assets in bankruptcy or similar event, Personal Information may be part of the transferred assets.
  * Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Sites. When you interact with content from our partners displayed on our Site, please be aware that you are providing your Personal Information to these third parties and it will be governed by their respective privacy policies.

OUR OPT-OUT POLICY

Sharing with Third Parties for Marketing. As noted above, we may disclose your information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you would like to opt out of such disclosures, please contact us at [press@rileyrose.com](mailto:press@rileyrose.com).

Email Marketing. To stop receiving newsletters or marketing communications from us or to opt out of having your email address shared with third parties, please use the “unsubscribe” mechanism provided in the communication or send an e-mail to press@rileyrose.com along with the information necessary for us to process your request.

Service-Related Announcements. We will also send you service-related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

OUR POLICY ON CORRECTING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION AND DEACTIVATING YOUR ACCOUNT

You may request to access, correct, update or delete your Personal Information, or deactivate your account, by emailing our Customer Support at [press@rileyrose.com](mailto:press@rileyrose.com) with information necessary for us to process your request. We will respond to your request to access your Personal Information within 30 days. We may need to verify your identity before granting access to Personal Information in our custody or control. Please see below regarding our retention policy.

MISCELLANEOUS

Other Websites. The Sites may contain links to third party owned and/or operated websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We suggest that you contact these third parties directly for information regarding their privacy, security and data collection and distribution policies prior to providing them with any information.

Blogs and Public Features of the Sites. Some of our Sites offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any Personal Information you submit there can be read and collected by other users of these forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages and for other purposes. Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. NONE OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE USING THESE FEATURES IS PROTECTED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO SUBMIT IN THESE FORUMS OR THE USE THEREOF BY ANY THIRD PARTY. You will need to contact or log into the third party application if you want the Personal Information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

Testimonials. We may post customer testimonials on the Sites which may contain Personal Information such as the customer’s name. We obtain the customer’s consent to post his/her Personal Information along with the testimonial, prior to posting the testimonial. If you want to remove your Personal Information that is being displayed on a Site under public pages, please send your request to [press@rileyrose.com](mailto:press@rileyrose.com).

Social Media Widgets. Our Sites may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets such as the share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Sites. These features may collect your IP address, which pages you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

Security and Retention. We take commercially reasonable steps to help protect Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from a Site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Information to us or to any other party via the Internet. The security of your Personal Information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms or login credentials (such as username and password) on our platform login, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Your Personal Information will be stored in the United States and will be subject to laws applicable in that country. If you have any questions about security on our Sites, you can contact us at press@rileyrose.com. We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

Minors. Visitors under 13 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information at any Site. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not submit any information to us. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

Contacting Us. Our “contact us” page contains e-mail links that allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments that you may have. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at [press@rileyrose.com](mailto:press@rileyrose.com) or at:

Innovative Brand Partners, LLC.

3880 North Mission Road

Los Angeles, CA 90031
